healthprofessor.com 2013-03-18

# Health Professor - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy Updated:** 01/03/2008

**HealthProfessor.com, HealthProfessorRX.com and its parent company HEALTHPROFESSOR, LLC.** , ("HealthProfessor" or the Company") understands the importance of online privacy. The following Policy outlines how we do business, what information we collect how your personal information is used and how we protect that information. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us. The HealthProfessor adheres to accepted healthcare industry privacy standards and practices.

This Privacy Policy applies to HealthProfessor and web sites owned and operated by HealthProfessor, LLC, including HealthProfessor.com and HealthProfessorRX.com. Information you provide may be shared with its subsidiaries but will always be protected by our Privacy Policy terms.

Please be aware that HealthProfessor.com contains links to other sites. Once you leave HealthProfessor.com through a banner, video, link, and etc. HealthProfessor is no longer responsible for your privacy. Always look for the privacy terms of each web site you visit through a link or ad on HealthProfessor. 

**Information We Collect And How It Is Used**  
In order to receive your free gifts and our newsletter, you must first complete the registration information requested. Registration automatically subscribes you to the HealthProfessor.com newsletter, a periodic email communicating the latest information on health related topics, healthcare industry reports and various offers that we think you might like based on the registration information you provided, and any offers that you selected in this promotion. Users may unsubscribe from this newsletter at any time by clicking on the automated "unsubscribe" link provided at the end of the email.

We request a limited amount of personally identifiable information from users who participate in the promotions on this site. This information includes, but is not limited to the following: 

  * email address 
  * name 
  * address, city, state, zip 
  * phone number 

We use this information to communicate with you about the status of your free software and/or any offers you have selected from our sponsoring companies. We request your address and phone number for shipping purposes and customer support issues.

HealthProfessor.com is committed to protecting the privacy of children. The web site is not intended for anyone under the age of 13 and we do not collect personally identifiable information on any person we know if under the age of 13. Parents and legal guardians using information provided by HealthProfessor.com for children assume full responsibility for the interpretation and use of any information or suggestions provided by HealthProfessor.com for the minor.

Third party ad agencies under contract with HealthProfessor may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personal information about your use of HealthProfessor and HealthProfessorRX.com. This information may be used to customize your experience and the ads we show you. This non-personal information is anonymous and does not contain personally identifiable information about you. If your cookies are disabled, this non-personal information will not be transmitted to our advertising partners.

We create internal reports on user demographics and traffic patterns to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and promotions, and to report results to our marketing partners. We do not use any personally identifiable information to compile these reports.

**How We Collect Information**

_The Company gathers information in the following ways:_

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. The Company uses cookies only to enable users to be routed properly through our site. We also provide links to external advertisers and marketing Partner companies; these sites may choose to use cookies to better promote their products and services. These advertisers and marketing partner companies have their own privacy procedures and policies that are not controlled by the Company.

We encourage our users to be aware of the individual privacy policies of every Web site that the user contacts. 

**Clear Gif's (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**  
The Company may also use a software technology called clear gif's (Web Beacons or Web Bugs), that help us determine what content on our site is most effective. Clear gif's are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gif's to our customers' personally identifiable information.

We also use clear gif's in our HTML-based emails so that we know which emails have been opened. We use this information to monitor the effectiveness of our email campaigns and to validate our results to our marketing partners.

**Log Files**  
Log files are also used to track and monitor traffic patterns on our site. They are not used to track or monitor personally identifiable information.

**Tell-A-Friend**  
Users may forward the email address of another person who may also be interested in this particular offer. The information is used only to forward the information to that person and is not retained for any other purpose.

**User Feedback/Inquiries**  
Users may contact the Company with any feedback, questions or comments. The Company uses contact information only to respond to the feedback.

**Other Circumstances**  
Subsequent to this promotion, the Company may sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events for which we need to collect and retain personally identifiable information. The Company may co-sponsor such events with other companies. 

**Information We Share**  
All information provided to the Company by the users of this site may be used to support our suppression, validation and enhancement services to other marketing companies, advertising agencies, compilers and data companies.

As an example, opt-out information may be shared with other marketing partners so that those users opting out of further offers are suppressed from the partner's mailings or promotions, as well as our own. In addition to complying with our users' preferences, it simply makes good business sense to mail only to those customers who have indicated a desire to receive such mailings. 

The Company's business model includes participating in affiliate network programs and other co-marketing partnerships to promote our site. We reserve the right to share with 3rd parties the information we collect on this site for any purpose.

**Use of Information**

This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on the HealthProfessor.com and HealthProfessorRX.com websites, and or have submitted their email address through our affiliate network program and other co-marketing partnerships to promote our site. We may use the personal information that you supply to us and work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via direct mail, email and telemarketing. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

**Delete/Deactivate Policy**  
Users at any time may unsubscribe to our electronic mailings by following the instructions that we include at the end of every mailing. To correct, update or request that we delete information you provided, please contact us via email, or by writing to:  
HealthProfessor, LLC  
5030 Champion Blvd. #154  
Boca Raton, FL 33496

**You can unsubscribe at any time by entering your e-mail address**[here](http://www.purelyunsub.com/)

**Notification Of Changes To Privacy Policy**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post these policy changes to our Web site to notify you and provide you with the opportunity to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

**General Security Policy**  
The Company endeavors at all times to meet and exceed standards of online privacy protection. When you submit information, your information is protected both on-line and off-line in accordance with applicable laws, regulations and industry standards. For example, without limitation, the company uses a full-time Network Administrator, SSL servers, pgp and 128-bit encryption to protect the confidentiality of the information you provide.

For additional information or specific questions, please contact us at:

HealthProfessor, LLC.  
5030 Champion Blvd. #154  
Boca Raton, FL 33496

Copyright © 2007-2008 HealthProfessor.com and HealthProfessorRX.com. All Rights Reserved.

The information provided herein should not be used during any medical emergency or for the diagnosis or treatment of any medical condition. A licensed medical professional should be consulted for diagnosis and treatment of any and all medical conditions. Call 911 for all medical emergencies. Links to other sites are provided for information only -- they do not constitute endorsements of those other sites. © HealthProfessor LLC. Any duplication or distribution of the information contained herein is strictly prohibited.
